Let's discuss the details of the machine learning workflow.
下面我们详细了解下机器学习流程
It's composed of three components:
它由三个环节组成
explore and process the data, modeling, and deployment.
分别是探索和处理数据 建模和部署
The first step is to retrieve the data.
第一步是获取数据
For a Kaggle competition, this is simple.
对于 Kaggle 竞赛来说 这一步很简单
We're given a dataset that contains
我们已经有一个数据集
all the housing data that we'll need to train our model.
其中包含训练模型所需的所有房价数据
Therefore, this step involves downloading the data in this case to CSV files.
这一步需要将数据下载到 csv 文件中
Next, we'll clean the data and explore the data.
下一步是清理和探索数据
This involves exploring and visualizing
我们将探索和可视化数据
our data to identify the most promising features like
并发现最有效的特征
relationships between housing values and
例如房价和房间数之间的关系
the number of rooms that can be used in the modeling component.
这些特征可以用在建模环节中
The data may also have to be cleaned to identify and remove
我们还需要清理数据
any anomalous values such as outliers or mistakes.
并发现和删除所有异常值 例如离群值或错误的值
The final step of this component is to prepare and transform the data.
这个环节的最后一步是准备和转换数据
Most machine learning models expect standardized data values.
大部分机器学习模型都要求输入数据是标准化数据
Therefore, this step often involves normalizing and converting the format of the data.
所以这一步通常还需要标准化和转换数据格式
In addition, this step is where the data is split into training,
此外 我们会在这一步将数据拆分成
validation, and test datasets.
训练集 验证集和测试集
Remember, the training dataset is used to train the model.
训练集用于训练模型
The validation dataset is used for model tuning and selection.
验证集用于优化和选择模型
The test dataset is used after training for evaluation of the model.
训练之后 我们使用测试集评估模型
The next component, modeling,
下个建模环节
focuses on developing the model that's deployed to production.
侧重于开发要部署到生产环境中的模型
The first step is where the model is developed and trained using the training dataset.
第一步是使用训练集开发和训练模型
The final step of modelling is to evaluate and validate the model.
建模的最后一步是评估和验证模型
In this step, you'll tune the model using the validation data set.
在这一步 我们将使用验证集优化模型
You'll also select the model if you've developed
如果在上一步开发了多个训练模型
more than one train model in the previous step.
还需要选择最佳模型
The final step is to evaluate your model using the test dataset.
最后一步是使用测试集评估模型
The final component of deployment focuses on deploying,
最后的部署环节侧重于
monitoring, and updating the model in the production environment.
监控和更新生产环境中的模型
This is what we'll be focusing on in this lesson,
我们将在这节课以及本纳米学位课程的后续课程中
and the rest of the nanodegree.
专门讲解这一环节
We'll start with deploying the model to the production environment.
首先 我们将模型部署到生产环境中
Simply put, this means making your model
也就是让网络或软件应用
available for use by web or software application.
能够使用我们的模型
For a Kaggle example,
对于 Kaggle 示例来说
we'll deploy the model to a smartphone application.
我们会将模型部署到智能手机应用中
This will allow application users to determine the worth of Boston houses based
使应用的用户能够根据房屋特征判断波士顿的房价
upon a house's features The final step is to monitor and update the deployed model.
最后一步是监控和更新部署的模型
With our example, imagine there's a tech boom in the Boston area,
在我们的示例中 假设波士顿地区出现了技术蓬勃发展现象
and it causes a dramatic increase in the median housing prices.
导致房价中位数飙升
To update your model,
为了更新模型
you'll build and train it using this new data,
你需要使用新数据构建和训练模型
and then deploy it as a new version of the smartphone application.
然后部署为新的智能手机应用版本
Application users can access the updated model by downloading the updated application.
用户可以通过下载更新的应用访问更新的模型
The cyclical nature of the workflow enables
这个流程的循环特性
user data captured during deployment to be used to create new models.
使在部署过程中获得的用户数据能用于创建新的模型
Specifically, the data captured during deployment can be explored and
我们会在第一个环节探索和处理
processed in the first component then
在部署过程中获得的数据
used to develop a new model on the second component,
并在第二个环节开发新的模型
and finally, deploy to
然后
the production environment in the third component of the machine learning workflow.
在机器学习流程的第三个环节将模型部署到生产环境中
Model deployment is often a critical aspect of machine learning in
模型部署通常是工作场所机器学习的重要组成部分
the workplace that's why it's good to keep the machine learning workflow in mind.
所以需要谨记这个机器学习工作流程